[
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the Canadian province of Saskatchewan?",
        "answer": "Regina"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the official name of the country of Mexico?",
        "answer": "United Mexican States"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Vermont?",
        "answer": "Montpelier"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Australian state was formerly known as Van Diemen`s Land?",
        "answer": "Tasmania"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most mountainous country in the world?",
        "answer": "Bhutan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the state Louisiana named after?",
        "answer": "King Louis XIV of France -- Explorer Ren\u00e9-Robert Cavelier named the area to honor his king. `La Louisiane` translates to `Land of Louis`."
    },
    {
        "question": "What countries share land borders with Cambodia?",
        "answer": "Thailand, Laos and Vietnam"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Cambodia once known as?",
        "answer": "Khmer Empire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Empire was Cambodia once known as?",
        "answer": "Khmer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Cambodia gain its independence from France?",
        "answer": "1953"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Cambodia declare its independence from France?",
        "answer": "1953"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what present-day country is Mount Ararat located?",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What present-day country is Mount Ararat located in?",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sea is located between Asia Minor and Greece?",
        "answer": "Aegean Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which sea separates Greece from Asia Minor?",
        "answer": "Aegean Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Georgia?",
        "answer": "Atlanta"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country was formerly known as Abyssinia?",
        "answer": "Ethiopia"
    },
    {
        "question": "In England, what is `Brown Willy`?",
        "answer": "A hill in Cornwall"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Russian newspaper`s name `Pravda` mean in English?",
        "answer": "Truth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continent would you find Morocco in?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    }
]